This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
Separated from the rest of his crew,
Luffy has finally arrived at Marineford to rescue his brother Ace.
The Whitebeard Pirates have successfully pushed into the Bay,
but a massive number of Marines still block the path to Ace.
The battle is spreading to the Bay Head,
where allies of Whitebeard are under attack from the Navy's human weapons, the Pacifistas.
Oh, Squad, good to see you're alive.
Yeah, barely.
Is that so? I was trying to reach you earlier.
How are things looking at the Bay Head now?
I'm sorry to say, but your allies were beaten pretty badly.
As for me, I only managed to get out of there through sheer luck.
Sengoku is one merciless bastard.
He's pulling out every dirty trick he can think of.
Judging by your shift in tactic, I'm guessing you picked up on the Navy's plan.
I've known Sengoku and what he's capable of for a long time.
Huh? What's Squad doing up there?
You have 43 allied captains willing to die for you.
We're all in your debt, for now and for always.
We consider it a privilege to risk our lives for you and your crew.
Huh?
Akainu's plot. Whitebeard entrapped.
Ones of the Deaf
Chilinder
Thank you.
Don't move, Pops.
You'll make things worse if you keep squirming.
Whitebeard.
I'm serious.
This battle is a fake.
Just ask him.
I know about your treacherous deal with the Navy.
You have their assurance that Ace and all of your pirates won't even get scratched.
They'll just go after your allies.
Wait, what's he saying?
Is it true that they're just targeting us?
Everybody, listen up!
Whitebeard's been playing us all for fools.
All this time, you've kept it a secret.
You didn't have the guts to tell me that Ace is actually the son of that wretched pirate,
Gold Roger.
When you first found me, I was alone in this world.
A complete wreck.
The sport is out of his mind again.
He's dangerous when he's like this.
Stay away.
Come on.
This again?
Once it starts, you just gotta sit back and ride it out.
Isn't there anyone strong enough to face me?
I'm right here.
Bring it on.
How's about Gold Roger?
Where's he at?
What's the matter?
Are you all scared?
Give me your best shot!
You knew why I was all alone that day.
My precious crew, who had fought alongside me in so many battles, was killed by Gold Roger.
You know this, and you know that I despise Roger, more than anything!
Yet you still kept these secrets from me, that Ace was Roger's son, that you were helping him become the next king of the pirates!
How could I trust someone like you?
Never mind the Whitebeard's son, that's why I'm going to help him become the king of the pirates!
That's why I'm going to help him become the king of the pirates!
The old guy, he wants Ace to be the king?
Because you see, Whitebeard's the greatest pirate I've ever met, that's why I'm going to help him become the king of the pirates!
You've been betraying me, and playing me for a fool since the very beginning!
I didn't have a damn clue!
I bet you laughed your ass off when I became friends with Ace!
Then your favorite son got caught, and you showed your true colors!
All of the Whitebeard pirates are inside the bay, while us Allied pirates are stuck outside!
Forty-three captains fight beside you, and you handed us all to the Navy, just to protect Roger's son!
We Allied pirates will be obliterated, whereas Ace and your men will be completely safe!
That's your underhanded deal with Sengoku, isn't it?
What? Firefist Ace is Roger's son?
That's right, and our superiors already have an agreement regarding how this war is going to end.
Go to hell! I don't believe a word of that crap!
Whether you believe it or not doesn't matter.
You're going to end up dead anyway.
That's enough! We'll see who ends up dead, you wretch!
You're a stubborn brat, but you'll learn what I'm talking about soon enough.
Stand up and look for yourself.
We plan to converge our forces soon, then attack the Allied pirates, only them.
And Whitebeard, the Navy isn't even going to lay a finger on his gang of pirates.
Not one of us knew the truth, and so we followed you, risking our lives to help rescue Ace,
only to find out we were nothing more than sacrificing to you!
We're the ones bearing the brunt of the Navy's attacks!
It's as clear as day!
Those monsters approach from the back, and the ice blocks us on both sides!
There's no way we can escape!
Whitebeard, old buddy!
Is he telling the truth?
He's lying his teeth off!
He's gotta be!
It's a miracle I was able to stab you.
Well, now it's your turn!
Kill me!
The ice wall is in the way!
We're blocked off on every side!
Oh, no!
Is this the end?
He was right!
Look!
The Navy's only going after us!
Run away!
Old buddy!
Please tell me we're not throwing our lives away!
Just so you can save us!
Please, say something!
Anything!
Whitebeard!
It can't be true. It's impossible.
Whitebeard wouldn't sell out fellow pirates.
He did that to his allies?
No way. He'd fight the Navy head-on.
Whitebeard and the Navy are in cahoots.
All those New World pirates who trusted and followed Whitebeard.
I know. I can't believe it.
They're all rushing to their doom thanks to his betrayal.
I didn't want to believe it.
We're all sons to you.
But I guess some kids are just worth more than others.
You're a damn fool!
The Navy is deceiving you, Squard.
Why trust them instead of Pops?
I know you're in on the deal.
Don't you play dumb with me!
You're the First Division Commander.
You're basically Whitebeard's right-hand man.
If anyone knows about his deal with the Navy, it's you!
It ain't Ace's fault his old man killed Squard's crew, but it is what it is.
And I can only blame myself for keeping it a secret all these years.
The Navy made the right move.
That doesn't make you any less of a bastard, though, Sengoku.
Even if you are a crafty one.
It's time to win this.
Go, Aokiji!
Oh, no!
Don't talk it up!
This entire war is a setup?
It can't seriously be fake.
I've wasted my whole day watching this stuff.
It shut off.
What's wrong?
Is it broken?
Now activate the walls.
Right!
The pirate who defeated me would never be struck down so easily, especially by his own ally.
You're not worth my time anymore, old man!
If this is how the Great Whitebeard dies, you'll make a fool of us both!
Oh, boy, that was harsh.
Then it was a matter of pride.
It's true.
He could have easily blocked that if he was as tough as he used to be.
It wouldn't have mattered that it was a surprise attack, or that it came from one of his allies.
Has Pops gotten weaker than we thought, and I just didn't notice?
I don't want no sympathy.
There's no way I'm wearing this crap in front of my enemies.
What, Pops?
He's letting his health get worse and worse.
I don't know if you realize the magnitude of what you've just done.
Squared, you thrust a sword into your father's body trying to kill him.
You've lost your way, my poor stupid son!
But I still love you, even if you are a damn fool.
Cut the crap.
You've sold our lives out.
All of us.
Who took your loyal and steadfast heart away from your father and delivered it into the hands of our enemies?
Now you tell me his name.
Aka'inu.
Admiral Aka'inu.
I'm opposed to such an underhanded plan.
Most people don't know the truth, so they call Whitebeard a hero.
They don't think twice about praising the man, but you know better.
He's a scumbag who came to us with a deal, one that protects his and his pirates' interests,
but betrays his New World allies without so much as a second thought.
All those stories and legends are made up.
The one we should kill in this war is Whitebeard.
Letting him live would be a great disservice to the world.
If you can help me, I'll save all of the New World pirates.
Whitebeard.
Kill him.
He said if I killed you, he would save your New World allies.
Aka'inu.
So that's what he told you.
I completely understand how much you hate Gold Roger.
So much so that I can feel your pain.
But listen to me.
It's ridiculous to lay the blame on a child for the sins of his father.
Did Ace ever do a thing to hurt you?
The two of you have been through so much together.
Some of it happy, some of it painful.
But you've weathered it all.
Good times and bad.
With our brothers in arms.
I never gave a damn about who Ace's father is, and I still don't.
We all crossed paths on these seas by chance.
And wherever the hell we came from doesn't mean a thing anymore.
We're together now.
So, squad, please treat him kindly.
I don't love Ace more than any other son of mine.
On that you have my word.
Every single one of you is part of my family.
Now, moving on.
That's Sengoku.
He hasn't changed one bit, the bastard.
But that crafty old snake gave us a pretty good shake-up, didn't he?
But to even suggest that I'd sell out my sons is ridiculous.
They can leave now.
He destroyed the ice wall.
He's a sharp one.
There's nothing blocking our path.
You're right.
We can take these Navy ships and sail away whenever we want.
If you're a true pirate, then you choose which path to take on your own.
I knew it was a lie.
The Navy's just trying to tear us apart.
Come on, guys.
Let's take it to them.
Of course they were lying.
Old Buddy would never betray us.
Hear that?
We'll die before we ever lose trust in you, Old Buddy.
Please forgive me.
We were wrong.
I'll follow you to the end, White Beard, Old Buddy.
Think I'm going soft, do you?
Give it a rest, Crocobum.
I'm only human, and every human has a heart, no matter how large or small.
People can call me a monster all they want, but the reality is I can't be the strongest pirate forever.
If I can save this one young man's life, I'll have earned the right to retire from this world once and for all.
Those of you who will still follow me, put your lives on the line!
It's ready, man!
He's coming his way!
The strongest pirate in the world!
Let's attack!
At last, the world's most powerful pirate, White Beard, leaps into the fray.
The Navy cowers in fear before the power of his Tremor Tremor Fruit, as it literally changes the landscape of the battle.
However, Sengoku has a plan that may yet turn the time.
On the next, One Piece!
The encircling walls activated, the White Beard Pirates backed into a corner.
I'm going to be king of the pirates!